<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Laxcon Steels Limited</string>

    <string name="companyDescription">With a focus to fit each client’s requirements. With its inception in 1978, <b>Gopal Group</b> of Industries today has established itself as a very well known player in the <b>global stainless steel industry</b>. Thanks to its strategic planning, ultra-modern facilities and exceptional team, Gopal Group has become a name to reckon with internationally. With a focus to fit each client’s specific requirements, the Group companies work hand in hand to produce the finest <b>stainless steel products</b>.

        Ever since its foray into the steel trade in 1978, <b>Gopal Group</b> has established itself as name to reckon with, in the steel industry. Over the years, through meticulous quality control and outstanding customer care, it has built a reputation for quality, reliability and integrity.

What started off as a small steel plant with a capacity of 2400 MT/year, Gopal Group has now grown into an organization with manufacturing facilities at multiple locations with a combined production capacity of 120,000 MT/year. Strong values of a family run enterprise backed by an assembly of industry’s most talented professionals has given the group its current form &amp; stature.

Today, Gopal Group’s wide range of products includeshigh quality SS bright bars, equal angles, Square &amp; Hexagonal bars, Flat Bars, Forged and Turned Round Bars, Forging quality Ingots and Concast Billets in over 100 Stainless Steel and alloy steel grades.

With sophisticated machinery procured from the best international manufacturers, Gopal Group boasts a full array of processes including Steel Melting Shops with an Argon Oxygen Decarburization (AOD) Converter, Ladle Refining Furnace (LRF), and Vacuum Oxygen Decarburization Converter (VD/VOD). Moreover, Gopal Group also has a Billet/Bloom/Round Twin-strand Continuous Caster of 9/16 Meter Radius, followed by heat treatment facilities and two 5 and 6 stand semi-automatic hot rolling mills. Our bright bar unit is also equipped with the most sophisticated technologies to deliver the highest quality stainless steel.</string>
    <string name="gopal_group_of_industries">Gopal Group of Industries</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="a_very_long_description_for_the_products">Our stainless steel bright bars are crafted with high finishing for superior quality and they are massively used in producing mechanical parts, owing to their paramount mechanical properties. Popular applications are found in the manufacturing of machine tools, parts of heavy machines, electric pumps, electric motors, railway engines, coaches, arms, ammunition, automobile parts and many more.
        Size range	5mm – 110mm (3/16″ – 4 1/3″)
        Supply conditions
        Length	Up to 6.5 meters
        Tolerances	h7, h8, h9, h10, h11, k12, k13
        Surface finish	RA upto 0.2 mm (8.7 RMS)
        Straightness	Up to 0.5 mm per meter TIR
        Grit polish	K240,K320 or as per customer’s requirement
        Heat treatment	Soft annealing, solution annealing, oil &amp; water quenching, tempering &amp; normalizing
        Bars end finish	Chamfered ends, 300, 450 &amp; 600 plain ends without burrs or sharp edges
        Specifications	As per EN, DIN, JIS, ASTM, BS, ASME, GHOST, AISI/Nace MRO175
        Cold drawn, centreless ground, peeled &amp; polished, rough peeled or smooth turned bar
        Grade Confirmation through PMI testing with Handheld Spectrometer.
        Free from radioactive elements, mercury &amp; lead contamination

    </string>

    <string-array name="array_calculator">
        <item>Calculate Weight of S.S Round Bar</item>
        <item>Calculate Weight of S.S Hexagonal Bar</item>
        <item>Calculate Weight of S.S Square Bar</item>
        <item>Calculate Weight of S.S Flat Bar</item>
        <item>Calculate Weight of S.S Angles Bar</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
